[{"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110205pmt", "aSentId": 16, "question": "Really?", "qSentId": 15}, {"answer": "Well, especially in this country because they usually get it wrong, say Sir Hopkins.", "docId": "110205pmt", "aSentId": 22, "question": "Do you?", "qSentId": 21}, {"answer": "Well, first of all, I looked at the script and I thought I don't want to do another weirdo, because I'm not - wasn't quite sure.", "docId": "110205pmt", "aSentId": 38, "question": "What was it?", "qSentId": 37}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110205pmt", "aSentId": 51, "question": "Was that what grabbed you, that it had happened?", "qSentId": 50}, {"answer": "Well, we had - I'll preface this by saying that, we had Father Gary Thomas, who is an exorcist.", "docId": "110205pmt", "aSentId": 75, "question": "But you believe there is a devil?", "qSentId": 74}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110205pmt", "aSentId": 79, "question": "And he was your expert on the film, was he?", "qSentId": 78}, {"answer": "I thought it was quite impressive, given it's now forgotten and all.", "docId": "110205pmt", "aSentId": 84, "question": "So what do you think of my - my Latin?", "qSentId": 83}, {"answer": "Oh, yes.", "docId": "110205pmt", "aSentId": 104, "question": "You?", "qSentId": 103}, {"answer": "It's all me.", "docId": "110205pmt", "aSentId": 111, "question": "How much of that is - is you?", "qSentId": 110}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110205pmt", "aSentId": 114, "question": "You put that in there, didn't you?", "qSentId": 113}, {"answer": "That's what I believe in.", "docId": "110205pmt", "aSentId": 116, "question": "And is that - and is that because you actually - that's really what you believe yourself?", "qSentId": 115}, {"answer": "Yes, I do.", "docId": "110205pmt", "aSentId": 125, "question": "Do you believe in God?", "qSentId": 124}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "110205pmt", "aSentId": 136, "question": "You don't like absolutism, do you?", "qSentId": 135}, {"answer": "I think it is dangerous.", "docId": "110205pmt", "aSentId": 141, "question": "You think that's dangerous?", "qSentId": 140}, {"answer": "Well, the safest answer I can give is I don't know.", "docId": "110205pmt", "aSentId": 165, "question": "You know, what do you make of that phenomenon?", "qSentId": 164}, {"answer": "He's done it, and he says some extraordinary things do happen, extrasensory perception things.", "docId": "110205pmt", "aSentId": 178, "question": "He's done this, doesn't he?", "qSentId": 177}, {"answer": "No, I can't have a cynicism.", "docId": "110205pmt", "aSentId": 184, "question": "Would you believe this movie if you didn't pretty more (ph) believe in this?", "qSentId": 183}, {"answer": "Oh, something, a crisis in my life, some 35 years ago, and I was hell bent on destruction.", "docId": "110205pmt", "aSentId": 189, "question": "What changed?", "qSentId": 188}, {"answer": "OPKINS: Oh, I - I did.", "docId": "110205pmt", "aSentId": 193, "question": "So it's a fact that you, in that moment, as an atheist, you decided to pray to God, did you?", "qSentId": 192}, {"answer": "Oh, dear God.", "docId": "110205pmt", "aSentId": 243, "question": "I mean, can you - can you still do it, with the same sinister face?", "qSentId": 242}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110205pmt", "aSentId": 245, "question": "You want me to do it again?", "qSentId": 244}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110205pmt", "aSentId": 255, "question": "Did you still get asked to do that?", "qSentId": 254}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110205pmt", "aSentId": 257, "question": "In a way, it's become almost your catch phrase?", "qSentId": 256}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "110205pmt", "aSentId": 264, "question": "Do you actually drink - do you ever drink Chianti?", "qSentId": 263}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "110205pmt", "aSentId": 267, "question": "Have you ever eat fava beans?", "qSentId": 266}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110205pmt", "aSentId": 279, "question": "It was one of the greatest terrifying characters ever, wasn't it?", "qSentId": 278}, {"answer": "They asked me the other day -", "docId": "110205pmt", "aSentId": 311, "question": "It's the whole thing, isn't it?", "qSentId": 310}, {"answer": "Yes, any vices.", "docId": "110205pmt", "aSentId": 323, "question": "Any vices?", "qSentId": 322}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "110205pmt", "aSentId": 332, "question": "You don't smoke, do you?", "qSentId": 331}, {"answer": "I have had everything taken out of me.", "docId": "110205pmt", "aSentId": 337, "question": "Or do you feel you've had your great feeling of exercising (ph)?", "qSentId": 336}, {"answer": "Oh, yes.", "docId": "110205pmt", "aSentId": 345, "question": "Have you?", "qSentId": 344}, {"answer": "It's not ruthless.", "docId": "110205pmt", "aSentId": 357, "question": "So you become more ruthless these days?", "qSentId": 356}, {"answer": "Yes, I am.", "docId": "110205pmt", "aSentId": 370, "question": "Are you - are you at peace with yourself these days?", "qSentId": 369}, {"answer": "OPKINS: No.", "docId": "110205pmt", "aSentId": 387, "question": "Do you still have that burning drive to achieve, to get the acclaim of your peer group?", "qSentId": 386}, {"answer": "Ah.", "docId": "110205pmt", "aSentId": 395, "question": "What would be the moment you'd replay, right now, if you have the chance?", "qSentId": 394}, {"answer": "That's my first nomination.", "docId": "110205pmt", "aSentId": 400, "question": "At that moment when you're sitting there and you - how many times have you been nominated before that?", "qSentId": 399}, {"answer": "I didn't think I was going to get it.", "docId": "110205pmt", "aSentId": 406, "question": "What's going through your mind?", "qSentId": 405}, {"answer": "Yes, it was.", "docId": "110205pmt", "aSentId": 412, "question": "Was that - was that the greatest rush you've ever experienced?", "qSentId": 411}, {"answer": "Oh, yes, the greatest in the world.", "docId": "110205pmt", "aSentId": 415, "question": "Incredible actors you're up against, are you?", "qSentId": 414}, {"answer": "I've been thinking of my father, because he died 10 years previous, on that very night.", "docId": "110205pmt", "aSentId": 419, "question": "What - when you're standing there, because I'm - I'm unlikely to ever get this moment, when you're standing there, who were you thinking of?", "qSentId": 418}, {"answer": "He probably smoked himself to death because he always smokes.", "docId": "110205pmt", "aSentId": 427, "question": "What would he have made of that minute you're there?", "qSentId": 426}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "110205pmt", "aSentId": 454, "question": "Did you know that?", "qSentId": 453}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "110205pmt", "aSentId": 456, "question": "Are you - are you perturbed (ph) by this?", "qSentId": 455}, {"answer": "Past, present and -", "docId": "110205pmt", "aSentId": 465, "question": "Who to you have been the greatest actors of all?", "qSentId": 464}, {"answer": "I think he is.", "docId": "110205pmt", "aSentId": 469, "question": "Is he - is he the greatest living actor?", "qSentId": 468}, {"answer": "Oh, I think the power of somebody like Brando or De Niro or Betty Davis, you know, going back through time.", "docId": "110205pmt", "aSentId": 476, "question": "What do you look for?", "qSentId": 475}, {"answer": "They have a grasp of everything.", "docId": "110205pmt", "aSentId": 485, "question": "What do you mean?", "qSentId": 484}, {"answer": "DiCaprio certainly and I think I'm a great fan of Matt Damon.", "docId": "110205pmt", "aSentId": 489, "question": "Who do you see of the younger crop today that have - that may have that?", "qSentId": 488}, {"answer": "No, it's not - it's not that.", "docId": "110205pmt", "aSentId": 498, "question": "Are you drawn to the darker art?", "qSentId": 497}, {"answer": "It should be - it's quite a large town.", "docId": "110205pmt", "aSentId": 506, "question": "Is it - where it is?", "qSentId": 505}, {"answer": "OPKINS: When I was born it's about 75,000, a lot smaller.", "docId": "110205pmt", "aSentId": 509, "question": "The population of it would be what?", "qSentId": 508}, {"answer": "Well, I thought it was just the thing you did was just to drink and get smashed.", "docId": "110205pmt", "aSentId": 519, "question": "How much more time did it bring you as a good actor, do you think?", "qSentId": 518}, {"answer": "I think you have to be -- yes, I think you have to have a bit of trouble in your life.", "docId": "110205pmt", "aSentId": 532, "question": "Do all great actors have to have some kind of demon?", "qSentId": 531}, {"answer": "It gives you the drive.", "docId": "110205pmt", "aSentId": 536, "question": "Does it give you the kind of tormented face that you need?", "qSentId": 535}, {"answer": "Yes, it's fun.", "docId": "110205pmt", "aSentId": 542, "question": "Do you like -- do you like being famous now?", "qSentId": 541}, {"answer": "Of course.", "docId": "110205pmt", "aSentId": 548, "question": "I tell you -- can I tell you a quick story?", "qSentId": 547}, {"answer": "Without a doubt, Jodie Foster.", "docId": "110205pmt", "aSentId": 573, "question": "Which of the actresses do you really most admire?", "qSentId": 572}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "110205pmt", "aSentId": 575, "question": "Do you stay in touch with her?", "qSentId": 574}, {"answer": "None at all.", "docId": "110205pmt", "aSentId": 580, "question": "None at all?", "qSentId": 579}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110205pmt", "aSentId": 590, "question": "Really?", "qSentId": 589}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "110205pmt", "aSentId": 594, "question": "You didn't suddenly start doing your little Hannibal act for old time's sake?", "qSentId": 593}, {"answer": "I just obey orders.", "docId": "110205pmt", "aSentId": 602, "question": "Is that true?", "qSentId": 601}, {"answer": "I think so.", "docId": "110205pmt", "aSentId": 613, "question": "Have you got better at marriage as you've got older?", "qSentId": 612}, {"answer": "You can't go back and second guess yourself.", "docId": "110205pmt", "aSentId": 622, "question": "If you had your time again -- this is your third marriage, would you have played things differently in your previous marriages?", "qSentId": 621}, {"answer": "I think it was just something to do with the post-war years.", "docId": "110205pmt", "aSentId": 634, "question": "Why do you love America so much?", "qSentId": 633}, {"answer": "They're terrific.", "docId": "110205pmt", "aSentId": 660, "question": "Steven Tyler and Jennifer Lopez with Randy?", "qSentId": 659}, {"answer": "Well, I don't know.", "docId": "110205pmt", "aSentId": 667, "question": "Do you miss a bit of that grit though?", "qSentId": 666}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110205pmt", "aSentId": 678, "question": "Isn't Randy one of your mates?", "qSentId": 677}, {"answer": "He's my only famous friend.", "docId": "110205pmt", "aSentId": 682, "question": "Is he your only famous friend?", "qSentId": 681}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "110205pmt", "aSentId": 687, "question": "Are you?", "qSentId": 686}, {"answer": "I went about two years ago, I think.", "docId": "110205pmt", "aSentId": 692, "question": "Do you go to the Oscars?", "qSentId": 691}, {"answer": "I don't know what it is.", "docId": "110205pmt", "aSentId": 704, "question": "Does it really?", "qSentId": 703}, {"answer": "Yes, as far away from --", "docId": "110205pmt", "aSentId": 707, "question": "Is that one of the reasons you live out in Malibu?", "qSentId": 706}, {"answer": "Well, I'm not going to say that.", "docId": "110205pmt", "aSentId": 711, "question": "Is there a lot of phoniness really that does on in the business?", "qSentId": 710}, {"answer": "Yes, I do.", "docId": "110205pmt", "aSentId": 720, "question": "Do you think there's been a sort of breakdown in priorities?", "qSentId": 719}, {"answer": "ORGAN: Of course.", "docId": "110205pmt", "aSentId": 738, "question": "If I wrote my own epitaph, it would be -- well, first of all, do you know Mel Blanc, the vocal guy?", "qSentId": 737}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110205pmt", "aSentId": 759, "question": "Because what we are about to see, Michelle, is your mother actually undergoing an exorcism for real, right?", "qSentId": 758}, {"answer": "Oh, absolutely.", "docId": "110205pmt", "aSentId": 778, "question": "Are these -- are these classic signs of somebody who has been, in your view, possessed by the devil?", "qSentId": 777}, {"answer": "It's a nightmare.", "docId": "110205pmt", "aSentId": 786, "question": "I mean, it must have been, as a daughter, just almost unbearable to watch this, wasn't it?", "qSentId": 785}, {"answer": "No, no, no.", "docId": "110205pmt", "aSentId": 790, "question": "Was there a time when your mother was perfectly normal or did she always have this?", "qSentId": 789}, {"answer": "Oh, yes, I do.", "docId": "110205pmt", "aSentId": 795, "question": "Do you remember the first time it happened?", "qSentId": 794}, {"answer": "Fifteen.", "docId": "110205pmt", "aSentId": 798, "question": "How old were you?", "qSentId": 797}, {"answer": "Yes, actually that looked like one of the first ones.", "docId": "110205pmt", "aSentId": 800, "question": "And it was a similar scene to the one we witnessed?", "qSentId": 799}, {"answer": "I do.", "docId": "110205pmt", "aSentId": 820, "question": "ORGAN: Do you believe that she was possessed by the devil or evil spirits?", "qSentId": 819}, {"answer": "Pat Reading was an exception.", "docId": "110205pmt", "aSentId": 830, "question": "So I guess the obvious question is, why would this happen to somebody like Patty (ph)?", "qSentId": 829}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110205pmt", "aSentId": 845, "question": "-- and she had 16 of these incidents where you had to bring a priest in, right?", "qSentId": 844}, {"answer": "No memory at all.", "docId": "110205pmt", "aSentId": 847, "question": "When she came around, did she have any memory of what had happened?", "qSentId": 846}, {"answer": "In the beginning, I didn't want to tell her everything.", "docId": "110205pmt", "aSentId": 853, "question": "Were you honest with her?", "qSentId": 852}, {"answer": "I don't believe that one, no.", "docId": "110205pmt", "aSentId": 857, "question": "Did you show her the video?", "qSentId": 856}, {"answer": "Basically, rule everything out from a medical perspective, a psychological perspective.", "docId": "110205pmt", "aSentId": 861, "question": "I mean, so for people who are watching this who may have a similar situation going on in their homes, how should they deal with this?", "qSentId": 860}, {"answer": "She had what they believe was pancreatic cancer or colon cancer.", "docId": "110205pmt", "aSentId": 871, "question": "Do you believe that they're linked in some way?", "qSentId": 870}, {"answer": "Well, the key factor with this is very seldomly (ph) an exorcism or a deliverance is very successful on one try.", "docId": "110205pmt", "aSentId": 882, "question": "I mean, why should people bother, John, in having these if they're not going to work?", "qSentId": 881}]